A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Lost Island.
Long ago, an explosion occurred here,
creating a dangerously strong magnetic field.
Now the island is the site of a battle
between the DWMA and Arachnophobia.
While members of both sides struggled for possession
of the magic tool brood,
three of us entered the magnetic field with our weapons
in search of Professor Stein and Miss Marie.
Waiting for us inside the field was a scene from the past,
frozen in time by that long-ago explosion.
I'm falling down to my shadow.
Let's do the opposite.
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby
怖い夢だとしても
テレブル君のために
星を砕き飾り付けた
Black paper
知りてくれたなら
When you're lost in one year
Forever with your soul
見上げれば輝く
月のように
Dammit, they just keep on coming
Now what?
We've almost reached the 20-minute mark
It's time, Kim
Give the signal for retreat
We'll watch your back
Okay, make sure I'm covered
You ready, Jackie?
Yeah
They're attacking Enforce again
Let's go, I got it
Resonance Link
Change Pixie!
I don't think so
Royal Thunder
Flash of Lightning
Thunder Combination
Good job, you guys
Thanks
Okay, now it's our turn, Jackie
Mosquito Storm
Ten minutes to fight in the world of the past
Where are they hiding?
Confirmed
Target sighted
Welcome
We have plans for you
One more step
Now
That's gunpowder
Spikes
All right, Nagus, I've got it
Do it
Will!
Die
i get it now if all teachers at the academy are like you i can see how blackstar became the
fighter he is you're a true professional samurai i can respect that what i don't get is why you'd
work for an organization like arachnophobia
it's such a waste
that signal an order to retreat
it's over we're being called off i have no more reason to attack you now
you can put down your sword and end this what'll it be
of course it may be safer to finish me if we do meet up again you may not be able to escape
i'll take that chance
go on
all troops withdraw withdraw
what's wrong
can you hear me what's happening
i'm drowning
the madness has me
you need to get a hold of yourself franken
madness
why is this happening now
it's like there's something eating him from the inside out
you have to watch me marie there's no telling what i might do
here they are
we've been looking all over for you guys
are you all right
you three what do you think you're doing here
i told you to stay out
you disobeyed me
it's been twenty minutes since you came in here
you need to get out
his body is beginning to blur
what about brew
we haven't been in long
it'll still be safe for ten minutes
we can look for the tool
let's go
hurry and get out
hey hold it
get back here now
i can't chase after them
we have to get out
but when we get back they're in big trouble
we already disobeyed orders
we might as well go all the way
where is this thing anyway
disobeying orders
what am i turning into
there's a gate up ahead
someone's there
is he part of the past
it seems like he noticed us
he looks familiar
i think i've seen him somewhere before
could that box he's got be what we're looking for
i expected to run into academy agents
but i didn't think they'd send three meisters
fresh from their play pens
all you have to do is hand over the box you're carrying old man
do that and you can be on your way
old man huh
don't underestimate me
little brat
consider my offer
have you looked at your body lately
my body
you're beginning to blur
you can't afford to stay in the field much longer
we've still got ten minutes left though
we won't even have to fight you
you'll become a memory before long
all we have to do is prevent you from leaving the magnetic field
and the rest will be taken care of for us
that's true
this old body can't handle more than 20 minutes in here
it's all right though
that can be fixed
shaving off a few years should give me plenty of time
four hundred perhaps
no no one hundred should be enough
go ahead call me old now
this is how i looked 100 years ago
this body should buy me an extra ten minutes
so now we're even
ew
his torso inflated so much
that his legs are dangling in the air
does that look right to you?
none of it looks right to me
not really an improvement
you three look quite tasty
i bet you have delicious young blood
who is this guy?
another memory?
just when things are about to get interesting too
we should be careful
he's here
abon
what did you just say?
is that really?
abon?
do you recognize him kid?
no
time's running out guys
we're down to less than 10 minutes here
we can't afford to mess around anymore
let's get him!
hand it over gramps
i may not know exactly what's going on here
but i know that tool is ours
abon's getting away
come on black star
no time for that kid
this show's ending in 10 minutes
we've got to prioritize
10 minutes is barely enough time for a star like me
to put in a decent appearance
you're pathetic
you think making yourself a few years younger
and a few pounds heavier
is gonna help against me?
don't make me laugh
hey!
black star's actually right this time
our first priority is getting brew
let's go
right
careful!
are you guys okay?
wake up kid!
right i know
we've got to take care of this guy first
clearly this man lacks any sense of symmetry
let's remedy that
right!
that's the spirit kid!
three little babies
is this all you're capable of?
they don't make them like they used to
this was me a hundred years ago
tougher and stronger than all three of you put together
no way
there isn't a single scratch on him
this is bad
we can't resonate souls as a team
not in this place
the static's too loud
Maka's the only one who could do it
her ability to perceive souls
is strong enough for this
what are we gonna do soul?
we'll never beat him
if we can't use resonance link
maybe i could direct her ability
and channel everyone's souls
what do you mean maybe?
you know you can do it
don't you
Evans?
don't call me by that name
damn it
come on
right this way
we're set up and ready to go for the big concert
look after the injured
the battle didn't go our way
you should look after your injury too
I will
soon enough
Sid!
Nygus!
we're here!
Kim!
Jacqueline!
glad you made it
what about the others?
well sir
the teachers never came back out
so Maka's team went in to find them
Ox and Killik are holding back the enemy
they did what?
Azusa
can you find the students?
no i'm afraid not
the field is too strong
i can't see them
it'll take 15 minutes to get there in this snow
Azusa
gather 10 people who can make the trek with me
Sid!
with those injuries you shouldn't
Nygus
quickly see to my injuries
all right
after the first wave our technique suffered a little bit
the enemy was rather strong but still
we could have done much better
who cares if we were a little sloppy
we won the fight didn't we
professor! miss marie!
what happened in there?
i need you to watch over the professor
what are you planning marie?
the effects of the field won't disappear just because you stepped out of it for a moment
go back in and you're throwing your life away
i know that
but if i don't what will happen?
you mean the rest of them are still inside?
then let us go in after them
no!
you're not going anywhere
i'm not letting any more of my students go inside that death trap
if you disobey orders you will be punished!
i'll expel you!
what are we gonna do now, Hawks?
you can't get expelled from the academy
i don't think we have much choice in the matter, harver
none at all
academy students protect their own
simple as that
they don't let brand new teachers go around expelling students
nothing threatening to stop them from going anyway
i can't even do that
they don't let brand new teachers go around expelling students
not the threatening to stop them from going anyway
i'm an adult
i'm their teacher
i can't do anything
what do i do?
i let them go
what if they never come back?
don't cry, marie
the failure of the mission
any harm that comes to the students
everything
it's all my fault
all of it
surely you've realized by now that you can't beat me
shut up! give us brew immediately!
you think you're such smart little children
can you even tell me what this magic tool inside my hat does?
heh heh, of course you can't
and yet you've come all this way and fought so hard to get your hands on it
the folly of youth has no end
you brats don't even know what you're fighting for
we have brew now
arachnophobia will soon control the entire world
you should run while you can
shut up grandpa
i'm tired of hearing you yammer
Tsubaki! enchanted sword!
great!
magic tool? who cares about that? not me baldy
this isn't a fight between arachnophobia and the academy
not anymore, it's between me and you!
maka, kid, follow my lead on this
shadow sword!
a puny attack like that's not going to do any damage to me you foolish boy
that was only round one i'll still take you down! at this rate we've got no chance
i'm throwing four! time to get rid of you!
had enough yet?
a little more
tiny bugs like you are easy to crush
come on guys!
it's time to get up now!
shall we pull the curtain down on this sad plane?
no the show's just beginning
right soul, let's get started
police stingers!
there's no more time to think about it!
the stage is all set for the big concert
it's time to play!
the black blood already spread to maka
this will spread it to everyone else on the team won't it?
your resonance with them will be an indirect connection
the blood won't spread if you don't resonate strongly with maka
come with me now to the black room let your soul sing together in sweet harmony while the
black blood runs faster and stronger throughout your veins i know i have to but do i have it in
me the piano will play and the madness will dance to the tune
what do i do
listen everyone we're going to resonate as a team using sound using sound but soul do you even know
how to do something like that i think so i thought of it a while ago back when we first learned about
linking souls together here's how it works our wavelengths communicate through maca
that's possible even here since your soul perception is so strong
i still don't see how we're supposed to resonate i'll play the piano with my soul
the sound will resonate directly with your soul wavelengths
i don't get it why is everyone laughing it's just that we've been trying to come up with a plan
you never want to play so we were gonna trick you into it and now you're offering to do it
unfortunately we can only stay in here for five more minutes so the concert will be a bit rushed
please play for us soul we're ready we've been looking forward to this for a while
yep
what do you think
good crowd tonight
everything's in place the piano's all tuned up and ready to be played
that's so
you
hey
Oh
I
Haven't heard so play in a long time
It'll be funny if he messes up button your shirt sit up straight hands in your lap
Hey, I'm not the one performing even audience members should have manners look souls about to begin all right
Let's hear it play to my soul soul
Oh
Anything on the next episode of soul eater unleash the seventh resonance link a recital of destruction and creation
Watch it or I'll take your soul